<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Meditation</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle"> A simple, fast way to reduce stress</string>
    <string name="article_text">If stress has you anxious, tense and worried, consider trying meditation. Spending even a few minutes in meditation can restore your calm and inner peace.
        \n\n
        Anyone can practice meditation. It\'s simple and inexpensive, and it doesn\'t require any special equipment.
        \n\n
        And you can practice meditation wherever you are — whether you\'re out for a walk, riding the bus, waiting at the doctor\'s office or even in the middle of a difficult business meeting.
        \n\n
        <b>Understanding meditation\n\n</b>
        Meditation has been practiced for thousands of years. Meditation originally was meant to help deepen understanding of the sacred and mystical forces of life. These days, meditation is commonly used for relaxation and stress reduction.
        \n\n
        Meditation is considered a type of mind-body complementary medicine. Meditation can produce a deep state of relaxation and a tranquil mind.
        \n\n
        During meditation, you focus your attention and eliminate the stream of jumbled thoughts that may be crowding your mind and causing stress. This process may result in enhanced physical and emotional well-being.
        \n\n
        <b>Benefits of meditation\n\n</b>
        Meditation can give you a sense of calm, peace and balance that can benefit both your emotional well-being and your overall health.
        \n\n
        And these benefits don\'t end when your meditation session ends. Meditation can help carry you more calmly through your day and may help you manage symptoms of certain medical conditions.
        \n\n
        <b>Building your meditation skills\n\n</b>
        Keep in mind, for instance, that it\'s common for your mind to wander during meditation, no matter how long you\'ve been practicing meditation. If you\'re meditating to calm your mind and your attention wanders, slowly return to the object, sensation or movement you\'re focusing on.
        \n\n
        For more information visit our site: https://www.mayoclinic.org/

    </string>
</resources>